driverboost.com 2016-12-23

# Privacy Policy | DriverBoost.com

#### DriverBoost Privacy Policy Effective Date: 05/5/2014

Boost Software, Inc. (DBA "DriverBoost") privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") covers the collection and use of personal information ("Personal Information") that we may gather any time you interact with us, such as when you visit our Web site, purchase a DriverBoost products, or when you contact our customer support or sales departments. This policy describes our data privacy practices, including what type of information is gathered, how DriverBoost uses the information, and how we safeguard your Personal Information when you submit it to us at www.driverboost.com. At DriverBoost, protecting your privacy is important to us. After all, online privacy and security is what we’re all about. **You expressly consent to the processing of your Personal Information according to this Privacy Policy.   Personal Information may be processed by DriverBoost in the country where it was collected as well as other countries (including the United States) where laws regarding processing of Personal Data may be less stringent.**

DriverBoost complies with the U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from European Union member countries and Switzerland. DriverBoost has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view DriverBoost’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>. 

**Why DriverBoost Collects Personal Information**

DriverBoost only collects your Personal Information where it is required to provide you the best services and products available. By maintaining an accurate customer database, we are able to send notifications via e-mail to keep you informed about the status of your orders or accounts and to provide updates and technical notices. These messages are essential to the maintenance of your subscription and the functionality of our products and services.

**Why DriverBoost Collects Device Hardware and Software Inventory Information**

DriverBoost collects your device’s hardware and software inventory information in order to deliver our driver and other device-associated recommendations, download access, and installation automations provided in our software.  The hardware and software inventory data is essential for our software and servers to match the best updates for a particular system on an ongoing basis.  We retain this information in order to continuously improve our matching intelligence based on aggregating and normalizing the data collected across all systems.

**What Information We Collect**

**Personal Information**

DriverBoost collects your Personal Information at a variety of points, including when you place an order, (which may require you to provide personal information, including a credit card number, to our commerce providers) register software, request services or take part in other activities on our Web site. For example, we often ask for your Personal Information when you are conferring with one of our customer support technicians, downloading a new product or program update, registering your software or purchasing a product. During these interactions we will collect Personal Information relevant to your transacting with DriverBoost, such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, shipping address and credit card information along with information about the DriverBoost products you own, such as the activation code or key code, date of purchase and information relating to a support issue. We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. When you register, you will be provided with an option to opt-out of receiving promotional information on our products and services. We will not use your personal information for anything other than what you have intended it for. Please be aware that if you prefer not to provide us with your Personal Information, because such information may be necessary for us to provide certain services, we may not be able to, or may choose not to, make such services available to you.

**Device Hardware and Software Inventory Information**

The scanning technology present in our software is designed to collect all hardware ID’s and software signatures present in the system and passes this data back to our servers.  We use this information so that our servers can respond back to our software with a list of recommended drivers and other software relevant to the discovered hardware.  While in trial-mode (pre-purchase) this information is not tied in any way to any personal information.  Post-purchase and after activation of the software the inventory data is linked to your personal information so that it can be shown as historical information in the software, used as part of our free driver backup service,  as well as historical scan information available in your personalized <https://secure.driversupport.com/account/> web portal (all features of our software and services).  This information is also used to handle any technical, product, or customer support requests that you may send to us.  Please be aware that if you prefer not to provide this inventory information, our software will be unable to provide any of our services.

**Regarding Children**

DriverBoost does not intentionally gather Personal Information about visitors who are under the age of 13.

**Cookies and Other Technologies**

Following common e-commerce practices, DriverBoost uses "cookies" and other technologies to collect non-personal data that enables us to better understand and improve the usability, performance and effectiveness of DriverBoost’ Web site, and for reporting purposes to track sales. Cookies are unique text files sent to your browser and stored on your computer. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. We use session cookies to maintain a login session. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. We use persistent cookies to help remember user preferences. We do not store any personally identifiable information with these cookies. Use of these third party cookies by our tracking utility company or service providers is not governed by this Privacy Policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies.

If you do not want DriverBoost to send cookies to your browser, you can set your browser options to reject cookies or notify you when a Web site tries to put a cookie in your browser software. Rejecting cookies may affect your ability to use some of our Web site services.

Additionally, DriverBoost gathers general information about visits to our Web site and stores this information in log files. This information is stored in anonymous profiles and is not associated with a user’s account. This information includes the number of total visits to our Web site, and which browser is used to view our Web site (including the version number). No Personal Information is contained in this data. Our current partners help us to track our website usage. No personally identifiable information is collected. DriverBoost uses this information to understand traffic and downloads on our Web site, enabling us to improve the site, provide the best online experience possible and improve our ability to serve our customers.

On occasion, DriverBoost also gathers general information about click-through usage of key features within our software to confirm that software updates are providing the intended user experience.  This information is collected in aggregate from and stored in a manner that cannot be associated with any individual.  The information includes total clicks on select features available in our software and is used to understand how our software is used, enabling us to improve the software, and provide the best possible user experience for our customers.

We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. Visitors can opt out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). We do not respond to a browsers do not track signal. 

**Sharing Your Personal Information**

DriverBoost is committed to protecting your privacy. DriverBoost will not, under any circumstances, share, rent or sell your Personal Information in ways other than as outlined in this privacy policy nor does DriverBoost trade or exchange mailing lists with any other organization. Furthermore, DriverBoost only shares your Personal Information with our contractors that assist us in our efforts to fulfill our obligations to you, and then only with partners that commit to adhere to the same level of commitment as DriverBoost to protect your privacy and data. We use credit card processing companies to bill you for goods and services, an email service provider to send out emails on our behalf and a customer support provider to supply live assisted-support. These companies do not retain share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

DriverBoost maintains this information; but we reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Website. If you require assistance, and would like someone to follow-up with you, then you will be asked to provide an email address. The email address is stored log files by a third party, but is not utilized in any way by them and remains our information.

If our company or our assets are acquired by another company, that company will possess the Personal Information collected by us and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. 

**How We Communicate with You**

DriverBoost has an optional e-mail service for customers who wish to periodically receive promotional information, such as general product, service and DriverBoost news. Users can sign up for emails through one of the following processes: (1) an online Purchase; (2) registering through the full application; (3) registering through the trial application; and (4) signing up on the DriverBoost website.

Customers are provided the option to opt-out within each e-mail. If you no longer wish to receive DriverBoost communications, you may "unsubscribe" from our mailing program at any time in the following ways:

  * By clicking on the auto-unsubscribe link included in each e-mail
  * By contacting our technical support department at support@driverboost.com
  * By visiting your **Account** page at <http://account.driversupport.com/> and changing your preference on the form. 

We will then update our database and take reasonable measures so that no further promotional correspondence should be sent to the e-mail address. You may, however, still receive transactional messages.

**Transactional Messages**

DriverBoost sends required notifications via e-mail to keep you informed of the status of your orders or accounts and to provide updates and technical notices. This service is used for messages that are important for the maintenance of your subscription and the functionality of our services. When you purchase or register a product online, we require an e-mail address for completion of the transaction, which we will use for these communications. In order to stop receiving these notifications, please contact our technical support team at support@driverboost.com. You will be opted out of further communications within 10 business days.

**Ways to Update Your Personal Information**

carefully maintains our customer database in an effort to keep your Personal Information accurate for the purposes for which it is used. It is your right to be able to update your Personal Information as needed. You can correct out-of-date information, update information, remove information, delete your Personal Information or review any information previously provided to DriverBoost by visiting the account settings page on. DriverBoost or by contacting our support department at support@driverboost.com. Changes will be implemented within 10 business days. We will also respond to access to personal information within 10 business days. Please note, however, that we may retain certain information relating to software licensing and your information for as long as your account is active, as needed to provide you services and may also be retained in our archives. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Please contact us if you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services. When contacting customer service, we will verify your identification through the use of security questions before sharing any Personal Information as it appears in our customer database. 

**DriverBoost’ Commitment to Data Security**

DriverBoost has security measures in place, such as the following, to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your Personal Information in our customer database. Personal Information provided to DriverBoost is stored in secure facilities with access restricted to authorized personnel only. We have put in place a series of access-control procedures required for retrieval of personal information. The DriverBoost Web site is regularly tested for security breaches to protect against unauthorized viewing of Personal Information.

To provide secure credit card processing when ordering, orders placed on our Web site are processed through a payment gateway which operates under its own privacy policy.

DriverBoost DOES NOT store credit card information. DriverBoost works with third parties to serve as a trusted intermediary to handle e-commerce transactions with our customers. Our commerce partners handle e-commerce on secure servers which encrypt all of our customers’ personal information. To learn more about how our commerce partners manage the privacy of information in conjunction with these e-commerce transactions, please see their complete Privacy Policy located on their purchase pages.

Although we make good faith efforts to store the Personal Information we collect in a secure operating environment that is not accessible to unauthorized users, we cannot guarantee complete security.

**Links to other sites**

Our Website includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of DriverBoost, LP. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit.

**Acceptance of this Privacy Policy**

By using the Web site or any services provided through the Web site, you expressly consent to the use and disclosure of information as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Privacy Policy Revisions and Notifications**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this policy, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, and by means of a prominent notice on our home page, posted 30 calendar days prior to implementing the change.

**DriverBoost.com Contact Information**

For questions about this policy as well as product-related technical support: [Click Here](https://secure.driversupport.com/account/support/contact/)

Send all other correspondence to:

**DriverBoost**  
75 Arlington Street, Suite 500,  
Boston, MA USA 02116 USA  
Phone: 512.373.3518  
Fax: 254.983.9179 [privacy@BoostSoftware.com](mailto:privacy@BoostSoftware.com)
